Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Accounting / Finance Records, 1882-1985
  - Alex, A.J. Chief Accountant, Comptrollers Office
    - Conference at J.M. Krafts Office, 1926; 63.07
    - Summarized Bills of Installation Costs, 1928; 63.08
    - Invoice Supervisor Duties, 1929; 63.09
    - Supply Contract, 1932; 63.10
    - Price Lists, 1931; 63.11
    - Western Electric Supplement 2, 1940; 63.12
    - Class C Stock, 1939; 63.13
    - Revenue Act of 1941 and Sales, 63.14
    - Pricing, 1942; 63.15
    - Class B Material, 1942; 63.16
    - Pricing Discount, 1948; 63.17
    - SNET and Western Union Agreements and Contracts, 1928-1948; 64.01 (Box 36:, Folder 1211)
    - Contract Notes, Agreements, Procedures, 1916-1938; 64.01 (Box 36:, Folder 1212)
    - Western Union Arrangements, 1914-1916; 64.02 (Box 36:, Folder 1213)
    - Accounting Costs and Western Union, 1916; 64.03
    - Western Union and ATT Settlements, Agreements, 1913-1935; 64.04 (Box 36:, Folder 1214)
    - Meeting Minutes for Location Change, Woodbury Telephone Company, 1929; 65.01 (Box 36:, Folder 1215)
    - Construction Costs and Woodbury Telephone Co., 1932; 65.02
    - Billing and Collecting, Woodbury Telephone Co., 1930-1942; 65.03
    - Records and Wartime Regulations, 1946; 66.0 (Box 36:, Folder 1216)
    - Price Regulations, 1942; 66.02
    - Study of Working Advances, 1948; 67.01 (Box 36:, Folder 1217)
    - Procedures and New Facilities, 1948; 68.01 (Box 36:, Folder 1218)
    - Retirement Unit Costs for Outside Plant Methods, 1946; 70.0 (Box 36:, Folder 1219)
    - Retirement Unit Committees and Correspondence, 1947-1954; 70.0 (Box 36:, Folder 1220)
    - Retirement Unit Cost Studies, 1954-1955; 70.01 (Box 36:, Folder 1221)
    - Accounts with US Government, US Army, 1945-1947; 112.9 (Box 36:, Folder 1222)
    - Cost Service Orders, 1948; 114.1 (Box 36:, Folder 1223)
  - Bound Volumes
    - Analysis of Reserve, 1904-1905 (Box 37)
    - Cash A, 1886-1887 (Box 38)
    - Cash D, 1882-1883 (Box 39)
    - Cash P, 1915-1916 (Box 40)
    - Equipment Expenses, 1889-1890 (Box 41)
    - Equipment Expenses, 1890-1891 (Box 42)
    - Expense Account 6, 1889-1890 (Box 43)
    - Expense Journal, 1885-1908 (Box 44)
    - Expense Ledgers
      - 1904 (Box 45)
      - 1905 (Box 46)
      - 1906 (Box 47)
      - 1907 (Box 48)
      - 1908 (Box 49)
      - 1909 (Box 50)
      - 1909 #2 (fragile) (Box 51)
      - 1909 #3 (fragile) (Box 52)
    - Intertown and Interstate Business (fragile), 1882-1886 (Box 53)
    - Intertown and Interstate Business (fragile), 1887-1890 (Box 54)
    - Journals
      - A, 1882-1884 (Box 55)
      - C, 1886-1888 (Box 56)
      - D, 1888-1891 (Box 57)
      - E, 1891-1895 (Box 58)
      - F, 1895-1900 (Box 59)
      - G, 1900-1905 (Box 60)
      - H, 1906-1910 (Box 61)
      - I, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Ledgers
      - A, 1882-1884 (Box 63)
      - B (with index), 1884-1888 (Box 64)
      - C, 1888-1890 (Box 65)
      - D (with index), 1891-1896 (Box 66)
      - E (with index), 1897-1902 (Box 67)
      - F, 1902-1905 (Box 68)
      - G (with index), 1906-1908 (Box 69)
      - H, 1908-1909 (Box 70)
      - I, 1909-1912 (Box 71)
      - J, 1913-1916 (Box 72)
      - K, 1917-1929 (Box 73)
      - 1929-1931 (Box 74)
      - General and Subsidiary Ledgers
        - 1931 (Box 75)
        - 1932 (Box 76)
        - 1933 (Box 77)
        - 1934 (Box 78)
        - 1935 (Box 79)
        - 1936 (Box 80)
        - 1937 (Box 81)
        - 1938 (Box 82)
        - 1939 (Box 83)
        - 1940 (Box 84)
        - 1941 (Box 85)
        - 1942 (Box 86)
        - 1943 (Box 87)
        - 1944 (Box 88)
        - 1945 (Box 89)
        - 1946 (Box 90)
        - 1947 (Box 91)
        - 1948 (Box 92)
        - 1949 (Box 93)
        - 1950 (Box 94)
        - 1951 (Box 95)
        - 1952 (Box 96)
        - 1953 (Box 97)
        - 1954 (Box 98)
        - 1955 (Box 99)
      - General Ledgers (in folders)
        - 1979 (Box 100:, Folder 1224-26)
        - 1980 (Box 100:, Folder 1227-29)
        - 1981 (Box 100:, Folder 1230-32)
        - 1982 (bound volume) (Box 101)
        - 1983 (bound volume) (Box 102)
    - Monthly Record of Business by Exchange
      - 1892-1894 (Box 103)
      - 1895-1897 (Box 104)
      - 1898-1900 (Box 105)
      - 1901-1903 (Box 106)
    - Monthly Reports
      - 1908-1919 (Box 107:, Folder 1233-39)
      - 1919-1923 (Box 108:, Folder 1240-46)
      - 1924-1926 (Box 109:, Folder 1247-53)
      - 1927-1929 (Box 110:, Folder 1254-60)
      - 1930-1933 (Box 111:, Folder 1261-68)
      - 1934-1936 (Box 112:, Folder 1269-74)
      - 1937-1940 (Box 113:, Folder 1275-81)
      - 1941-1944 (Box 114:, Folder 1282-89)
      - 1945-1948 (Box 115:, Folder 1290-96)
      - 1949-1953 (Box 116:, Folder 1297-1302)
      - 1954-1958 (Box 117:, Folder 1303-07)
      - 1959-1962 (Box 118:, Folder 1308-12)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 119:, Folder 1313-16)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 120:, Folder 1317-20)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 121:, Folder 1321-24)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 122:, Folder 1325-29)
      - 1960-1985 (year end, December only) (Box 123:, Folder 1330-33)
    - Petty Ledgers
      - A, 1895-1899 (Box 124)
      - B, 1900-1901 (Box 125)
      - D (includes index), 1902 June - 1903 August (Box 126)
      - E, 1903 September - 1904 November (Box 127)
    - Plant Ledgers
      - 1904 (Box 128)
      - 1905 (Box 129)
      - 1906 (Box 130)
      - 1906 (Box 131)
      - 1907 (Box 132)
      - 1908 (Box 133)
      - 1909 (Box 134)
      - 1909 (Box 135)
    - Register of Audited Vouchers
      - 1910-1911 (Box 136)
      - 1910-1926 (Box 137)
      - 1927-1930 (Box 138)
    - Speaking Tube Account #3, 1884-1897 (Box 139)
    - Subscribers Instruments Gains and Losses (flat box) (Box 140)
      - 1887 to 1891 June (fragile) (Box 140:, Folder 1334)
      - 1891 July to 1894 December (fragile) (Box 140:, Folder 1335)
      - 1895 (Box 140:, Folder 1336)
      - 1896 (Box 140:, Folder 1337)
      - 1897 (Box 140:, Folder 1338)
      - 1898 (Box 140:, Folder 1339)
      - 1899 (Box 140:, Folder 1340)
      - 1900 (Box 140:, Folder 1341)
    - Subscribers Ledger Southington Exchange, 1911-1912 (Box 141)
    - Trial Balances (bound books)
      - 1882-1884 (Box 142:, Folder 1342)
      - 1884-1887 (Box 142:, Folder 1343)
      - 1887-1890 (Box 142:, Folder 1344)
      - 1890-1896 (Box 142:, Folder 1345)
      - 1896-1897 (Box 142:, Folder 1346)
      - 1901-1905 (Box 142:, Folder 1347)
      - 1906-1910 (Box 142:, Folder 1348)
      - 1911-1912 (Box 142:, Folder 1349)
      - 1913-1916 (Box 142:, Folder 1350)
      - 1916-1918 (Box 142:, Folder 1351)
      - 1914-1917 (Box 142:, Folder 1352)
      - 1917-1919 (Box 142:, Folder 1353)
      - 1918-1920 (Box 143:, Folder 1354)
      - 1920-1921 (Box 143:, Folder 1355)
      - 1921-1922 (Box 143:, Folder 1356)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 143:, Folder 1357)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 143:, Folder 1358)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 143:, Folder 1359)
      - 1925 (Box 143:, Folder 1360)
      - 1926 (Box 143:, Folder 1361)
      - 1926-1927 (Box 143:, Folder 1362)
      - 1927 (Box 144:, Folder 1363)
      - 1928 (Box 144:, Folder 1364)
        (includes prepaid and accrued expenses)
      - 1928 (Box 144:, Folder 1365)
      - 1929-1930 (Box 144:, Folder 1366)
      - 1929 (Box 145:, Folder 1367)
      - 1930 (Box 145:, Folder 1368)
      - 1931 (Box 145:, Folder 1369)
      - Loose Pages (Box 146)
        - 1884-1889 (some incomplete) (Box 146:, Folder 1370-75)
          - 1896-1902 (Box 146:, Folder 1376-82)
          - 1903-1913 (Box 147:, Folder 1383-93)
      - Condensed Trial Balance and Statement of Business
        (bound books)
        - 1891-1894 (Box 148)
        - 1894 December to 1897 (Box 149)
        - 1898 to 1903 March (Box 150)
        - 1903 April to 1907 (Box 151)
      - Condensed Trial Balance and Statement of Business
        (loose sheets)
        - 1890 March, June (Box 152:, Folder 1394)
        - 1891 (Box 152:, Folder 1395)
        - 1892 (Box 152:, Folder 1396)
        - 1893 (Box 152:, Folder 1397)
        - 1894 (Box 152:, Folder 1398)
        - 1895 (Box 152:, Folder 1399)
        - 1896 (Box 153:, Folder 1400)
        - 1897 (Box 153:, Folder 1401)
        - 1898 (Box 153:, Folder 1402)
        - 1899 (Box 153:, Folder 1403)
        - 1900 (Box 153:, Folder 1404)
        - 1901 (Box 153:, Folder 1405)
        - 1902 (Box 154:, Folder 1406)
        - 1903 (Box 154:, Folder 1407)
        - 1904 (Box 154:, Folder 1408)
        - 1905 (Box 154:, Folder 1409)
        - 1906 (Box 154:, Folder 1410)
        - 1907 (Box 154:, Folder 1411)
        - 1908 (Box 154:, Folder 1412)
    - Voucher Books
      - #1, 1888 November (Box 155)
      - #2 1889 (Box 156)
      - #3 1889-1890 (Box 157)
      - #4 1890 March - July (Box 158)
      - #5 1890 September - December (Box 159)
    - Vouchers for Construction, 1903 (Box 160)
    - Voucher Distributions, 1888 (Box 161)
    - Voucher Distribution Books
      - #1, 1891 January - July (Box 162)
      - #2, 1891 July - 1892 September (Box 163)
      - #3, 1892 October - 1893 December (Box 164)
      - #4, 1894 January - 1895 January (Box 165)
      - #5, 1895 March - 1896 June (Box 166)
      - #6, 1896 July - 1897 October (Box 167)
      - #7, 1897 November - 1899 March (Box 168)
      - #8, 1899 April - 1900 May (Box 169)
      - #9, 1900 May - 1901 July (Box 170)
      - #10, 1901 August - 1903 January (Box 171)
      - #11, 1903 February - October (Box 172)
      - #12, 1904 (Box 173)
      - #13, 1905 January - July (Box 174)
      - #14, 1905 August - 1906 February (Box 175)
      - #15, 1906 March - October (Box 176)
      - #16, 1906 October - 1907 April (Box 177)
      - #17, 1907 May - November (Box 178)
      - #18, 1907 December - 1908 July (Box 179)
      - #19, 1908 August - 1909 March (Box 180)
      - #20, 1909 April - December (Box 181)
  - Depreciation Accounting
    - Accounting Report #7 Station Movement and Growth, 1962 (Box 182:, Folder 1413)
    - Accounting Report #7 Station Movement and Growth, 1963-1964 (Box 182:, Folder 1414)
    - Average Plant Investment/Depreciation and Amortization, 1922-1936 (Box 182:, Folder 1415)
    - Depreciation and Amortization, 1913-1932 (Box 182:, Folder 1416)
    - Depreciation and Amortization, 1913-1932 (Box 182:, Folder 1417)
    - Depreciation Correspondence
      - 1912-1926 (Box 182:, Folder 1418)
      - 1923-1952 (Box 182:, Folder 1419)
      - 1927-1930 (Box 183:, Folder 1420)
      - 1931-1935 (Box 183:, Folder 1421)
      - 1934-1950 (Box 183:, Folder 1422)
        (includes Board of Directors Minutes 1933-51)
      - 1936-1952 (Box 183:, Folder 1423)
    - Depreciation Reserve Accruals, 1920-1925 (Box 183:, Folder 1424)
    - Depreciation Reserve Accruals, 1926-1932 (Box 183:, Folder 1425)
    - Depreciation Reserve Requirements, 1933 (Box 184:, Folder 1426)
    - Depreciation Reserve Requirements, 1936 (Box 184:, Folder 1427)
    - Depreciation Reserve Requirements Study
      - 1933 (Box 184:, Folder 1428)
      - 1933 (Box 184:, Folder 1429)
      - 1936 (Box 184:, Folder 1430)
    - Instructions
      - Northwestern Bell Accounting Instructions, 1929 (Box 184:, Folder 1431)
      - Plant Accounting Instructions, 1924-1928 (Box 184:, Folder 1432)
      - Plant Accounting Instructions, 1924-1928 (Box 184:, Folder 1433)
      - Standard Sub-accounts Instructions, 1932 (Box 184:, Folder 1434)
    - Report of Depreciation Charges of Telephone Companies, 1934 (Box 184:, Folder 1435)
    - Report Rulings, 1934-1951 (Box 185:, Folder 1436)
    - Revenue Reports to FCC and PUC, 1968-1981 (Box 185:, Folder 1437)
    - Station Accounting
      - Committee Minutes, 1957-1959 (Box 185:, Folder 1438)
      - Correspondence
        - 1956 (Box 185:, Folder 1439)
        - 1957 (Box 185:, Folder 1440)
        - 1963-1965 (Box 185:, Folder 1441)
      - Procedures
        - M222, Vol. 1, Parts 1-7, 1956 (Box 185:, Folder 1442)
        - M222, Vol. 2, Parts 8-13, 1956 (Box 185:, Folder 1443)
        - M222 and M222-1, Parts 1-7, 1957 (Box 186:, Folder 1444)
        - M222 and M222-1, Parts 8-13, 1957 (Box 186:, Folder 1445)
      - Questions and Answers and SNET Studies, 1956 (Box 186:, Folder 1446)
      - Retirement Units (Box 186:, Folder 1447)
        - Station Equipment, 1926-1952
        - Outside Plant, 1926-1952
      - Retirement Units, Station Equipment, 1953-1966 (Box 186:, Folder 1448)
  - General Accounting
    - Ansonia Telephone Company Documents, 1897-1901 (Box 187:, Folder 1449)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1883-1884 (Box 187:, Folder 1450)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1901-1919 (Box 187:, Folder 1451)
    - Cancelled Debentures, 1893 October
      - 1-30 w/indexes (Box 187:, Folder 1452)
      - 31-57 (Box 187:, Folder 1453)
      - 58-100 (Box 187:, Folder 1454)
      - 101-130 (Box 187:, Folder 1455)
      - 131-165 (Box 187:, Folder 1456)
      - 166-200 (Box 187:, Folder 1457)
      - 201-230 (Box 187:, Folder 1458)
      - 231-265 (Box 187:, Folder 1459)
      - 266-300 (Box 187:, Folder 1460)
      - 301-321 (Box 187:, Folder 1461)
      - 451-485 (Box 187:, Folder 1462)
      - 486-531 (Box 187:, Folder 1463)
      - Debentures, 1983 January (Box 187:, Folder 1464)
    - Circulars
      - Bulletins and Circulars, 1910-1926 (Box 187:, Folder 1465)
      - Bulletins #3 and #8 and Circulars #7 and #8 (Box 187:, Folder 1466)
      - Cancelled Accounting Circulars, 1910-1927 (Box 187:, Folder 1467)
      - Cancelled Accounting Circulars, 1912-1916 (Box 187:, Folder 1468)
      - Cancelled Circular #8, 1913 (Box 187:, Folder 1469)
      - Circular Letters, 1887-1891 (Box 187:, Folder 1470)
      - Circular Questions and Answers, 1913-1916 (Box 187:, Folder 1471)
      - Circular History and Changes, 1891-1928 (Box 187:, Folder 1472)
      - Circular #8, 1912 (Box 187:, Folder 1473)
    - Continuing Property Records, 1943 April
      - Forms (Box 187:, Folder 1474)
      - General Statement (Box 187:, Folder 1475)
      - Inventory Forms (Box 187:, Folder 1476)
      - Location Records Routine (Box 187:, Folder 1477)
      - Practices and Records (Box 187:, Folder 1478)
      - Recommendations (Box 187:, Folder 1479)
      - Routines and Practices (Box 187:, Folder 1480)
      - Woodbury Telephone Company CPR (Box 188)
        - 1943-1947 (Box 188:, Folder 1481)
        - 1948-1950 (Box 188:, Folder 1482)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 188:, Folder 1483)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 188:, Folder 1484)
        - Excess Profits Tax, 1950-1952 (Box 188:, Folder 1485)
        - Inventory Sheets, 1950 (Box 188:, Folder 1486)
    - Comparative Balance Sheets, 1940-1942 (Box 188:, Folder 1487)
    - Comparative Balance Sheet (OS), 1942-1943 (Box 217:, Folder 1488)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 188:, Folder 1489)
    - Correspondence (original numbered order)
      - 20.12-20.14 FCC and Bookmakers (Box 188:, Folder 1490)
      - 20.15-20.18 Reports to FCC (Box 188:, Folder 1491)
      - 20.8-20.10 Responses to FCC (Box 188:, Folder 1492)
      - 20.11 FCC Annual and Monthly Reports (Box 188:, Folder 1493)
      - 20.1-20.4 FCC Accounting Circulars (Box 188:, Folder 1494)
      - 20.5-20.6 Uniform System of Accounts (Box 188:, Folder 1495)
      - 20.7-20.7A FCC Uniform System of Accounts (Box 188:, Folder 1496)
      - 36.2 Plant Inventories (Box 188:, Folder 1497)
      - 36.3 Plant Inventories (Box 188:, Folder 1498)
      - 36.6-36.11 Continuing Property Records (Box 188:, Folder 1499)
      - 48.1 Excess Profits Tax (Box 188:, Folder 1500)
      - 48.1 Excess Profits Tax (Box 188:, Folder 1501)
      - 48.1 Taxes (Box 188:, Folder 1502)
      - 74.3 and 126 Message Toll Settlement Contracts (Box 188:, Folder 1503)
    - Credit Debit Journal and Journal Details (OS), 1977 May (Box 217:, Folder 1504)
    - Depreciation
      - Accounting Papers, 1907-1929 (Box 188:, Folder 1505)
      - Charges Reports to ICC, 1924-1931 (Box 188:, Folder 1506)
      - Charts, 1930 (Box 188:, Folder 1507)
      - Data, 1933-1934 (Box 188:, Folder 1508)
      - Deductions in Income Tax Returns, 1940-1952 (Box 189:, Folder 1509)
      - Pamphlets, 1923, 1927, 1939 (Box 189:, Folder 1510)
      - Regional Conferences, 1928-1929 (Box 189:, Folder 1511)
      - Reserve Analysis, 1913-1940 (Box 189:, Folder 1512)
      - Reserve Data, 1959-1966 (Box 189:, Folder 1513)
      - Reserve Data, 1967-1971 (Box 189:, Folder 1514)
      - Service Life and Plant Mortality Manuals, 1927 (Box 189:, Folder 1515)
    - Development of Equity Invested Capital, 1942-1949 (Box 189:, Folder 1516)
    - Disbursement Vouchers, 1941 (Box 189:, Folder 1517)
    - Division Expense Summary, 1885 July (Box 189:, Folder 1518)
    - Docket #14700 Bell System Brief, 1923 (Box 189:, Folder 1519)
    - Docket #14700 Bell System Brief, 1928 (Box 189:, Folder 1520)
    - Emergencies
      - Flood Data Casualty Loss, 1955 (Box 189:, Folder 1521)
      - Flood Data; Taxes Depreciation Newspaper Clippings, 1955 (Box 189:, Folder 1522)
      - Flood Emergency Expense File, 1936 March (Box 189:, Folder 1523)
      - Flood Emergency Expenses, 1936 March (Box 189:, Folder 1524)
      - Hurricane Emergency Information, 1938 September - October (Box 189:, Folder 1525)
      - Hurricane Emergency Ledgers, 1938 September (Box 189:, Folder 1526)
      - Hurricane Estimate Information, 1944 (Box 189:, Folder 1527)
      - Hurricane Station and Line Data, 1938 September - October (Box 189:, Folder 1528)
      - Service Life and Salvage Studies, 1932 (Box 189:, Folder 1529)
    - Equipment Expenses, 1897 (Box 189:, Folder 1530)
    - Estimates for Statistician, 1959-1960 (Box 189:, Folder 1531)
    - Estimates for Statistician, 1961-1964 (Box 189:, Folder 1532)
    - Excess Profits Tax Estimation, 1950 (Box 189:, Folder 1533)
    - Excess Profits Tax and Developments, 1950-1952 (Box 189:, Folder 1534)
    - Excess Profits Tax Forms (OS), 1942-1943; note: see box 217, folder 1535
    - Exchange Service Rates, 1920-1925
      (includes area maps and tables) (OS)
      note: see box 217, folder 1536
    - Expenses Bills and Receipts, 1894-1896 (Box 189:, Folder 1537)
    - Expense Forms, 1910 (Box 189:, Folder 1538)
    - FCC Monthly Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 217:, Folder 1539)
      (includes separation sheet) (OS)
    - FCC Special Investigation/Patent Structure of Bell System, 1937 February (Box 189:, Folder 1540)
    - Handbooks
      - Cancelled Pages Part IV, 1953-1969 (Box 190:, Folder 1541)
      - Commercial Expense Accounts, 1933 January (Box 190:, Folder 1542)
      - Drop Wire Supports, 1927 (Box 190:, Folder 1543)
      - General Circular #301.2, 1957 (Box 190:, Folder 1544)
      - General Office Salaries, 1933 July (Box 190:, Folder 1545)
      - Line, Cable Placing and Splicing, 1932 February (Box 190:, Folder 1546)
      - Line, Cable Placing and Splicing, 1935 March (Box 190:, Folder 1547)
      - Miscellaneous Codes and Accounts, 1935 January (Box 190:, Folder 1548)
      - Miscellaneous Codes and Accounts, 1942 (Box 190:, Folder 1549)
      - Miscellaneous Codes and Accounts, 1949 (Box 190:, Folder 1550)
      - New England Telephone and Telegraph, 1962 (Box 191:, Folder 1551)
      - Outside Plant Forces, 1942 (Box 191:, Folder 1552)
      - Outside Plant Forces, 1949 (Box 191:, Folder 1553)
      - Preparation of Accounting Reports, 1941 (Box 191:, Folder 1554)
      - Preparation of Accounting Reports, 1950 July (Box 191:, Folder 1555)
      - Preparation of Accounting Reports, 1952 January (Box 191:, Folder 1556)
      - Revenue Accounting, 1946 (Box 191:, Folder 1557)
      - Sales Manual, 1932 (Box 191:, Folder 1558)
      - Station Installation and Maintenance, 1931-1934 (Box 191:, Folder 1559-61)
      - Stations No. 50 Coin Collector Installation, 1927 (Box 191:, Folder 1562)
      - Temporary Accounting Instructions for Buildings, 1933 January (Box 191:, Folder 1563)
      - Traffic Expense Accounts, 1933 January (Box 191:, Folder 1564)
      - Transmittal Notice, 1962-1963 (Box 191:, Folder 1565)
    - Handbooks (bound books) (Box 192)
      - Cancelled Pages, Parts I-III, 1953-1969 (Box 192:, Folder 1566-69)
      - General Accounting Handbook, 1953-1955 (Box 192:, Folder 1570-72)
      - General Accounting Handbook Revisions, 1964-1969 (Box 192:, Folder 1573)
    - Inventory Sampling Manual (OS), 1975 (Box 217:, Folder 1574)
    - Ledgers
      - Depreciation Books
        - 1948-1954 (Box 193)
        - 1955-1961 (Box 194)
        - 1962-1965 (Box 195)
        - 1966-1972 (Box 196)
      - Journal and Cash Record
        - 1975-1977 (Box 197)
        - 1977 December - 1980 February (Box 198)
        - 1980 February - December (Box 199)
        - 1981 (Box 200)
        - 1982 (Box 201)
        - 1983 (Box 202)
    - Outside Plant Engineering Practices, 1927 September (Box 203:, Folder 1575)
    - Procedures (Bell Subsidiaries)
      - Bell Telephone of Canada, 1968 May (Box 203:, Folder 1576)
      - Cincinnati and Suburban Bell Telephone Co. Parts I and II, 1963 July (Box 203:, Folder 1577-78)
      - Illinois Bell Telephone Co. Plant Accounting Practice Parts I-IV, 1960-1961 (Box 203:, Folder 1579-85)
      - New York Telephone Co. Accounting Handbook Parts I and II, 1960 January (Box 203:, Folder 1586-87)
      - Northwestern Bell Telephone Co. Field Accounting, 1963 March (Box 203:, Folder 1588)
      - Pacific Bell Telephone and Telegraph Co. Acct Handbook Parts I, II, 1960 (Box 203:, Folder 1589-90)
      - Pacific Bell Telephone and Telegraph Co. Plant Acct. Parts I and II, 1957-1963 (Box 203:, Folder 1591-94)
      - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Co. Plant Accounting, 1963 January (Box 204:, Folder 1595)
      - SNET Line Construction Parts I-III, 1963-1964 (Box 204:, Folder 1596-98)
      - SNET Line Construction Manual Parts I-III, 1963-1964 (Box 204:, Folder 1599-1601)
    - Property Lease, 1888 (Box 204:, Folder 1602)
    - Rate Case Exhibits, 1947 (Box 204:, Folder 1603)
    - Rate Case Information, 1947 (Box 204:, Folder 1604)
    - Rate Loops and Distances, 1891 November (Box 204:, Folder 1605)
    - Real Estate and Equipment Codes, 1976-1978 (Box 204:, Folder 1606-08)
    - Retirement Unit Costs, 1977-1978 (Box 204:, Folder 1609-13)
    - Retirement Unit Costs for Cable, 1978 (Box 204:, Folder 1614)
    - Retirement Unit Costs Development Data, 1978 (Box 204:, Folder 1615)
    - Spending Vouchers, 1920 (Box 204:, Folder 1616-20)
    - Spending Vouchers, 1920 (Box 205:, Folder 1621-28)
    - Station Accounting
      - Correspondence
        - 1957-1958 (Box 205:, Folder 1629)
        - 1958 April (Box 205:, Folder 1630)
        - 1958 July (Box 205:, Folder 1631)
        - 1959 (Box 205:, Folder 1632)
        - 1959 October (Box 205:, Folder 1633)
        - 1960 (Box 205:, Folder 1634)
        - 1961 (Box 205:, Folder 1635)
        - 1962 (Box 205:, Folder 1636)
        - 1963 (Box 205:, Folder 1637)
      - Cost Factors, 1970-1978 (Box 205:, Folder 1638-39)
      - Cost Factor Study Data, 1976-1977 (Box 205:, Folder 1640-41)
      - Guidelines for Sample Estimates, 1974 (Box 205:, Folder 1642)
      - Material Usage Study, 1975-1977 (Box 205:, Folder 1643)
      - Memoranda, 1972 (Box 205:, Folder 1644)
      - Minutes, Exhibits and Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 205:, Folder 1645)
      - Movement Estimating, 1957 (Box 205:, Folder 1646)
      - Sample Inventories, 1956-1958 (Box 205:, Folder 1647)
    - Station Apparatus Estimates, 1968-1978 (Box 206:, Folder 1648-49)
    - Station Apparatus Instruction Manual, 1971 (Box 206:, Folder 1650)
    - Station Apparatus Inventory Instruction Manual, 1971 (Box 206:, Folder 1651)
    - Station Growth Reports (OS), 1919-1928 (Box 217:, Folder 1652)
    - Subscribers Trial Balance, 1886 February (Box 206:, Folder 1653)
    - Tax Assessing Forms, 1959 (Box 217:, Folder 1654)
      note: see box 217, folder 1654